In the stead, whispered voice from somewhere far below
For I spoke a word, which made us screams that can't be heard
Televisions flickering the rain
Every channel broadcasting the same pain
Shadow figure standing in the hall
Waiting for the moment
Ancient waking underground
The darkness distance of starting moving
I searched the edge of every map
Where prophets whispered through the flame
I chased the crowns of borrowed kings
Until I forgot my own true name
The loudest wars would never fall
With sharpened steel beneath the sun
The deepest battlefield was hidden
It comes a river, every thought becomes a sea
Flex the voice within, become the truth you wish to see
It is never inside the kingdom control
Its face, as itself as caution
Keeping me in the same old place
The silence taught a deeper lesson
Every monster or my skin
God was lost, speak with power, words can build, words devour
God your tongue, God your mind
Every sentence shapes your life
Teacher, the student, the temple
Whenever separate is not stressed
You said that I'm fine, I don't think they can kill me
Shut the fuck up and sit down
Bossy droppings, boy in the fucking frown, anti-heroine
Cause you're watching Twitch and holding a hammer
I got other kids in peace and in picture reminds me of something
Fuck it, keep the door off the hinges from inside and jump your ass
Swing and be like this is sobering
Smashing on your brain stem but slinging is splashing
My name is too, I'm not the human
I'm the master hiding under the skin plotting a pretty good problem solving
I live in my world to make believe it's anity
Demons and horrors love to beat them nightly
Burn holy charcoal, ice and mist and tea
The world is so lettering
Come watch me cry as I wear the bones of the predators bathing in rock and gore like I'm completely free
Mean anything, radiance of insanity, derived from the relentless body black
Oh, I said I was too naked, yes I am
So now I told him that you all died your brain out
Slamming door and like shit on fire in the hall
Backfucking TNT
The lanterns in the last etero
It was a secret place
Brass until the gears will turn and moon
I flow between the scenes
Like somebody built a cathedral out of star
I'm so sick of being criticized by people that aren't even on camera, nor have they shown
very much of their lives themselves.
I show everything and everything's lied about, exaggerated, and I have actual, you can see
every episode, but anyway, I don't want to.
Well, on that movie, I will get on camera later.
I'm just, I just decided to stream on the new tonight
and I can't be on camera right now.
So I'm just a nude back here.
I'm not really nude.
I'm wearing him to speed though.
Okay, anyway, so anyway,
after like seeing something tonight,
like, you know, and how he spoke to me
the past couple of days,
it's like I just have to sever the relationship
What I don't even know what it is the weed or whatever it is
Tethering Brandon to the show. Hey ghost is free Alexander McQueen is free, you know BD got free
I mean thing that is is you know almost there. Yeah, you're free Brandon. So just go to your own show, okay?
I'm telling me I'm a PDF. You're gonna threaten me and stuff like that. All I all I did was take shit for you
But uh, yeah, I see how some people you know
People gratitude plus, you know, it's like I know and then he's doing the same
I mean, it's like I see how he talks to in X2 and it's like abusive. I mean, it's I said and it's
And I see the abusive to everybody eventually. I mean, it's like if he was nice at first, you know
If you can go back to this person, which he's very I mean, he was nicer than he is at least now and now he's
You know gone off the deep end, but
You know
And we'll just kind of like chill out on all the negative bullshit.
I mean, it's just been so intoxic and I don't want to like just feed into it.
So I mean, everyone can have their own show.
There's other shows that will talk about this all day.
If you want to talk negative shit, you can go beat it all day, you know?
And so we're happy to whine about everything.
Wow, she had a phone call from somebody. I mean, it's like wow
You know, how about you just block their number or something or don't answer?
You know, it's like not even the biggest deal
Does it need to be talked about for hours that you know, maybe someone was trying to reach out to you that maybe
Work things out or something. I don't know
there's a lot of pieces in the air, you know, but
Yeah, I really did I don't know exactly what happened to like I know
He he blew up at Alex and then it's like and then it maybe it seemed like
Wow, I set this all up. So he would like, you know
Get mad out. I I didn't know he I mean, I did know that he has a temper and stuff
And he I already severed with myself, but I wasn't gonna tell her what to do
And she doesn't tell me what to do with the friendship. That's how kind of I was trying to keep it
So I don't know if it was like, you know
she abducted by aliens and some other it's an alien or something took over and for like the next few months
I don't know what will happen, but it's like, you know
Then the day I don't hate anybody. I just want to like have fun and do my own show
I mean it's like not even like that even complicated. So even if there's nobody here
I have nightbot to talk to.
Nightbot is a great conversation.
See, that's all the shit nightbot is saying today.
Every time I talk, nightbot talks back practically.
And tell me the weather.
I mean, useful information.
See, I have the gong there, too.
So it's like, also, remember people, you can use the gong, too.
I mean, it's like, if you don't like people on the show,
I would just like say, ah, yeah.
The part of the show is having people I don't like,
so it's like some people will kick them off.
It's like, I don't know.
Maybe that's a flawed business plan. I guess it's not that well. Yeah, I wouldn't like that
I mean I mean people have made hundreds of dollars literally almost a thousand dollars off of just me
you know being kicked off of their show just because
The hate against me is so I guess stronger than the love, but did I deserve that?
No, not really. I mean, it's like, I mean, really tell me the worst thing I ever did to anybody. It's like what I'm
Or if you'll say my cats are abused. No, they're not abused. They're perfectly fine. They're perfectly healthy. We're really happy
But they're all they're all rescues. Okay. All my cats are rescues, you know
Hi, Rudy. Come here, babe. You hook. I'm running out
Rudy, Rudy, you're getting old. It's terrible, but um,
Come on, Rudy. Okay, but he comes running out. Come on
Come here, come right out.
Aw, Rudy.
I just hope it's like not, you know.
I don't know, she's just gotten a little bit more,
more, you know, he's getting older.
It seems like, it happens he's 18 years old, you know.
Anyway, I hope you had a good fourth of July.
It was a fun day for the most part, basically.
Didn't really do very much.
I mean, I just,
And then tonight, you know, I had my last cigar.
I have a couple beers and I'm all set for tonight.
Actually, I'm all good for tonight.
But, you know, it's okay.
I mean, it's like, really, it's like, if I need to,
I can restart from, well, I will have to, you know,
as I'll have to restart from like, you know,
scratch since obviously,
This is like also writer or say writer spider Wiggins goes wins the last time any of your
Cats have gotten their shots or been to a vet. Well, I would say that was Lola
After she had the second my litter kittens and then all the kittens had their shots too, but
Yeah, so it was Lola
Then her last thing and Rudy has a shot since 18 years old and Lenora had her shots all her shots
She had all her cycles of shots and so
And she hasn't been sick or anything and so and she is spayed all the cats are spayed and neutered
So do you have a problem spider awakens?
Or you're just trying to like, you know
Throw, you know fuel in the fire or something like that your arguments done
You asked me the question I answered honestly, but to say honestly
It's kind of obvious my cats are like healthy well taken care of it's just like such lies that they're
You know like you know dying and I have AIDS, you know if I have AIDS and it's like yeah
Then they're dying too, but I don't have AIDS, you know, I don't have sex really. I mean, it's like it's crazy
Let's you get AIDS from like, you know
Watching, you know some hairy guy flex for 45 minutes, but
Hey, I didn't have fun jokers or mr. Extend those channel though. He had this guy named. What's this guy's name?
Tyler or something, it was Tyler or something, but,
or no, Peyton, I called him Peyton.
It's a simple question, I answered the question,
what are you gonna be a bitch about it?
Maybe it's, you have a problem, you have a problem with you.
Get out of here, beat it.
I answered the stupid question,
and it was a very condescending question
that I've answered a million times before.
And it's like, I'm gonna be sick of answering it,
you know, it's like, if no one listens,
they're just gonna make up their own lie about it, right?
You geez go away. I don't and guys I was like and I'll kick out whoever I feel like it for any reason I feel like it
so
Don't even worry about it. I have to check my list to see if everyone wasn't hidden though because I do have road mods and I do have
Some psychopaths there, you know having their sights right now, but you know, I've dealt with
We're psychopaths in these ones
So I'll be okay. There's a reason I was like, you know
I got so into Satanism as a teenager, I never really realized, I was like, you know, I was like, why would, why would I study it so much, but it's like, but not like, dedicate myself to it because I couldn't because it was like too negative and mean.
It was basically just a locale philosophy, which is like, oh, let's laugh at people, let's be cruel.
It's a, and people are just our entertainment or Carol or blah, blah, blah, we're the, we're the God, we're the special people, blah, blah, blah, and blah, blah.
institutionalized narcissism just like most religions but you know some there's good in some religion i suppose but it's like you know
I would never really ascribe to any particular religion other than you know
I do have some deities that I do have a relationship with
They're deities of outcasts and pollution and things like that not even like you know
But also art and music and you know creativity
So, you know, sometimes you take the good with the bad, but you take them both and there you have the facts of life, right?
Hi Rudy, so he's running out again. I clean the hell out of my house. I clean my kitchen floor.
You can see the table sign is clear, so I put the camera up there. I put the little gong out if anyone wants me to hit the gong.
I'll get in my speedo and I'll hit the gong.
For a hundred dollars. I'm just kidding
Let's see. Yeah, I got all the stuff. I got my decks organized. I got oh
My gosh, it just feels so good to clean you get everything bad out of the house
And then it's like it's like it's a purge and I purged a lot of things lately
I purged, you know Alex McQueen and I purged
Ghosts, I mean and these were these were terrible terribly uncomfortable bow movements. You have to I mean imagine
I mean it's like Alexander McQueen was so full of cocaine I'm still high and then ghost I mean he's just like you know
That's not a good sounding meow. I know he's old. He's old. He's like 18 years old
I mean, it's like he's gonna you know, sometimes cats live till around 20, you know
He's seems like he's in a healthy shape. But yeah, he's and he doesn't the thing is he doesn't have a meow either
He doesn't really have a meow. This is his first time he's meowing. He was maybe he's getting better
I don't know he started meowing finally, you know, but he used to never meow. He used to like have a silent meow
so maybe
I don't know. I just don't know. Maybe he's meowing because he likes to hear me out,
because he hasn't meowed since I've gotten him. Have you ever heard him meow? No, he hasn't meowed.
So it is a good sounding meow to me. It's like, you know, somebody can't speak and then they say,
Ghost has a key energy facts. I know I mean it's like so gross and then I mean he gets into these things
Oh come defend me on a panel. I'm a ghost you just got you just said accidentally that you fucked your dog on
The show like I'm your cat when her phone was on and stuff and you didn't explain it. You should you should have said
Oh, you heard it wrong or something.
But you said, oh, I miss misspoke.
I mean, that's not a very good excuse.
I would never, I can only say, oh, I fucked my dog.
Oh, I meant, I was fucking around.
I don't know.
It just doesn't sound right to me.
But it's like, you know, I don't know.
And then Ghost writes to me, oh, I'm on to you, bubby.
And then he's like,
You know, he's he's calling I an exit all hours sending her links to be this panel and everything
She's like I don't want to go. He's just he's obsessed ghost take a chill pill
I mean, it'll be welcome back, but I mean, it's like,
I mean, so everyone will be welcome back
pretty much especially if they,
but they need to be kissing my toes at this point
and apologizing.
I mean, some of these people, I mean, it's like, Jesus Christ.
I mean, I have been through like such slander, abuse
and misunderstanding and I'm not even listening
or not even talking to me about things.
It's just running over to cause of all this drama.
I mean, it's like, the fuckery is beyond anything.
It's like, basically,
You know, I've decided I'm basically, you know, I'm pretty much gonna be disappearing from here
You won't see me. You only you won't figure out my new channels or anything like that. I'm not gonna go lives anymore
I'll be a totally faceless channel
right just putting out my putting out my
Hmm, but my transmissions and stuff like that
Because like what nobody wants to talk to me anyway, and it's like and then it's like I mean it's just like so crazy. It's like
Like there's very little I mean, it's a very little like I guess everyone no one like really likes me to begin with because how can you like, you know, it's like
Everyone like I mean, it's like everyone has been through the stupid scan
I mean, it's like I mean, of course I doubled down on this one because
The certain other things involved is like, you know, I can try walking in my shoes. Just stumble my ups
Yeah, hold on. We have a guest coming up
Hi. Hey psyche. How are you?
I'm okay. How are you doing tonight? I'm doing good. This baby's doing so good and I'm so happy
I got her before the fireworks and all she's happy and she learned to use a litter box and
I had a teacher to cover her poop
So before she uses a big litter box the machine or whatever that my other cats use I'm training her on the
Box that I got her
Yeah, oh my gosh
And she learned and she's here and they're going to be happy tomorrow, you know, and I'm going to go let them know that I did get her and she's been with me.
I got this I got this this kit and it had to get some litter in it or say I had to buy my own litter but has this basically this
Plastic ring system they put over your toilet and you start popping out the rings
You know and the cats eventually get toilet trained and so what oh really?
I mean where do you get those rings of the kitty was trained that way?
I mean it was hard to train ever she learned
on Amazon, I'm under like, I'm kid, city kiddie, I think.
It's like the city kiddie or something like that.
Say kiddie, kiddie, sit, do you mean like that?
City kiddie, like a city.
Oh, city kiddie, okay.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, because, yeah,
yeah, kiddie learned to do that for years a long time ago.
And then she just kind of learned in,
Yeah.
Yeah, the other ones couldn't, I heard about that.
I have a bullet, but I have a bullet.
cat that like took to it, his name was Oliver, he's unfortunately, he's not with me anymore,
I think he's still alive, but you know, he, he's kind of like, he's kind of a wild cat
and he's a toilet, I mean, I was completely shocked, but yes, it does work, but you have
to kind of stick to it, but it's pretty good, but it does like, you know.
I mean, it's so much better than, I mean, the, I hate dealing with litter, that's why I like having my cats be in the rubber cats because it's like, litter is just like, I mean, it's clay and it's like, I mean, it's like, I mean, there's all this.
You're getting this clay soaked in shit and carrying around. I mean, I don't know just this is just weird to me
Cuz cats like to go outside. I mean, you know if they can't but I mean, but there's done this great litter boxes
I mean, there's great. Yeah, I've got some good
I got that machine one or whatever. It's you know, but she's little and you know, she's eating good and
She's really happy and she follows me around and I take her places
So yeah, and I went out yesterday
Apparently Alex doesn't know how to do life because I went out with friends and celebrated my birthday
We went to a Mexican place too and got manudo and they did the tres leches cake and and had a little birthday party for me
Where the sombrero and they sing and and candles and stuff. So it was pretty nice
Yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, and then I'm kind of like, you know, Rudy
Rudy has like a little that little whining me out right now, but it's like and then someone's saying oh my god
Well, you know, it's like we're he's about to you know, he's about to die and stuff like that. He's 18 years old
I'm just gonna yeah, okay. He died at 20. So what happens? It just happened and they get older and sometimes I mean
It's like and so I mean it's like until you figure out cat immortality
Canada cry or whatever
You know, it's like, I'll do what I have to deal with.
You don't have to worry about if my cats have back here
and have their shots and stuff like that,
because they're my cats and they do have those things.
And I wouldn't have the cats, okay?
And so, you know, I'm also,
I have a legal number of cats too.
I mean, that's why it's like, you know,
everyone tried everything to get me in trouble for anything.
And it's like, no.
That's crazy.
Yeah, and it's mostly people online
or whatever that do that.
Over here, I'll get a lot of support.
And,
And they know they you know, they know how many cats I have and they gave me permission because these are the feral cats that we save
Yeah, yeah, they don't count as like necessarily a household member the feral cats because they go yeah
They gave me permission. They're they're the ones that insisted that I get this baby. Yeah
I mean, yeah, it does really help the cities too because, you know, like, like my city doesn't even have a have a pound
But that's because people don't even like, you know, it like take
They'll adopt the cats before they take a cat to the pound, you know, so there's no I mean
I'm like literally every cat here is either, you know, and that's something unfortunate happen
Like with this in the street or the coyote, then they can't fine. There's another house or there there's actually it's plenty of
like there's a plenty around here it's like there's a pier down there where
there's just like fish and you know like there's restaurants everywhere there's
I mean there's people that are love cats and so you know I just let the cat you
know yeah okay and uh can Joe join yes you mean Joe a real man you may join you
like Joe right
That was cool, but there's a lot of bullshit drama going on with that nut that lying on me when she has no friends at all
I was out with real life friends that you know that I've known for years
And one time I did a video from
It's uh, yeah this place a few years ago. I'm sure some videos they have and she knows I have real life friends
She doesn't have any and it's sad. I think it's just like, you know with with with her and us
I think it's just like, you know, she's got so mad about the Brandon thing and then it's like us maybe like she didn't see us like, you know
Sticking up for her and it's like I mean I try I did try I mean to the I mean at least the audience
I didn't have to hit him that day, but
Here he is
Oh, no, I'm sorry. I don't need to be rude. You're having a good time. I'm not an exes. I need to see a real domestic violence
Right here. I was just kicked. Oh my god
Person I was just kicked in my back
Yeah. No, I was just saying, you're like, oh, yeah, you ever got crotty chicks?
Hmm. Are the police about to be there?
Do you call the police show? What? Are you seriously?
You just got hit. Really? Somebody called a cop.
I couldn't call them. I'm too emotional.
Because somebody called the police.
I should get a roundhouse to the back.
Oh, my God. Did she? What did she do?
Pretty much. Yeah, pretty much.
Roundhouse came through the spine.
And Kim, Kim, you're crotty.
He's telling you to roundhouse.
you know side me I don't want to be rude like Kim's like a typical dull liberal like when she don't win her argument
She just like get physical like oh, I'm gonna hit you now
I mean it seems like both sides can be like that, you know, there's they're all ready
They're both the extreme sides of both parties. I'd like I say it's two wings. Oh, you want me to beat her
Uh, no, I want you to be
Oh, I thought that was they that's only said both sides was equal like it or two. Yeah
Yeah, never
It's nice to see you second. Oh, look at that fucking light. That's awesome. Is that an alien?
Yeah, that's a real alien. It's really cool. A real alien
I came inside my house. I mean wait see you see your electric bill wait see you see your fucking electric bill
My mouth will fall off my face. I look like the alien
We're gonna do it. Do you want to do an Eiffel tower on the alien guys?
Try it. Yeah, you can you can do that do an I can tell your hands up in the air touch Joe's hands
You know what a dirty Sanchez this oh my god, no
I don't know
What is the Cleveland steamer? Oh cleaver steamers when you like hold a woman down do you think it literally get shit right her forehead?
Cleveland steamer hot dog that these
I'm sorry
The Cleveland what I have no idea
didn't have a team I'd say one day I would well I know I would settle with them all bad up beat is this
That's one thing I will say. Well, I think I will get lost in the bush before it gets anywhere near your butthole
But hey
I would assess the beta but I get caught in the cobwebs like I'm caught in the bush
do you know that um you know a google maps can't even save people from from betas bush i mean it's
like they maybe it's like impossible i mean i say it's like no you actually go to the google maps
and type in the webs and then meet his best friend so i can she's crazy the way she mutes people and
doesn't want the truth said you know and then you gotta come up on the panel and she mutes you
Joe, no, she's talking to me.
Who are you talking to?
All right, well, she's better than Bita.
She's better than my baby Bita.
I am better than Bita.
Everybody knows that.
He didn't have anybody to prove it.
You know, she's a drunk.
She's drunk and all the time. It's that Joe. So, yeah, she's a loser and she lost all her ex-friends and lied
Basically that's it said oh it's based on her information from her shows, but she's like yes
I mean I said an INX is like, you know in a hospital bed
And she doesn't want her young camera because the caretakers will be seen behind her. Yeah, I don't have no caretakers
And he saw me FaceTime Joe yesterday
which is walking in the sun in like a, in shorts and a
Oh
And that's not me man, look at that. She's crazy
I know
It's Tommy James in the far left and that's uh, well it's supposed to be in X, but then there's Brandon Q
He's like see he's looking over at my money, and then there's me look at the ball
Tommy James is a real
And Tommy James looking at my money too, or he's you know thinking about asking I and he's got money. Yeah
They both have money in their hands, but they're looking at my money
I see I have my mind on my money their pocket watching me, but they have money in their hands
And you imagine walking sluggy like yes
Can you press that panic button? I think it's time that panic button. I like that
I actually have one of those that work actually about it staples that was a panic button and you just I mean
That's probably what she has you know at her place back because she doesn't have any real life people she ever
Is with I have been I mean I've been videos from Sam's boat and
That other friend that celebrated her birthday because you know and Alex we talked about it
What where does she doesn't have any real life friends at all not even family and it's sad
I don't need me room, but my friend came that's here with me. She would take a bullet for me
So do you have friends that would take a bull? Yeah, baby. Yes real life friends. Yes
Yes, I do and I do the same for them and especially family especially my family, you know
Yeah, I'm sorry. Yeah, I'll take a bull. It's like y'all take two bulls from our boys. I do
Especially they shoot me right up the asshole like damn
They're good
Here you go like damn really I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Yeah, yeah, but your people take cheetos. I'm Joe. I'm sorry
Okay, and then why aren't you asking me why don't why don't you ask beat it a cam up? She never cams up for an eight anybody
She never had
Yes, she did
Like Carl said when he came on panel
Member did member beat a cams up. Oh, yeah, she did earlier. Thank you, beat up
I'm saying right now
Yeah, that's her cam that's ways without camp cartoon
She never shows herself
devilized me
Filters no, she doesn't because I've he's seen me people see me she has a crater
Don't call me dude.
I don't know you.
I don't know you because you're drunk like she is all the time.
I don't care.
She uses a lot of filters because she's got bumps all over her eyes.
I have her real pictures.
She's mad.
She's that jealous.
No, I'm not she's a liar and she's a scammer and she stands far away in the dark so you don't see her face
So yeah, her face is
Drunk goggle eyes, but I don't want to talk about Vita. You're the one that brought her up. We didn't mention her
What happened what happened with clumsy
well we have this picture from the gay website we don't have been showing it here
we have that picture oh my god what is he got like an apple in his mouth
coffee so yeah we called him this week so right because the brand was like oh he is he's on a
gay website but it turns out he has a um aside business a side hustle i guess you would call it
um but he does and i'm gonna show you his side hustle i found the actual footage of where
let me see his side hustle at least okay you want to see his side hustle okay i'll pull it
I'm sorry.
Where did you get that picture?
Um, that was, you know, brand new.
None of your business.
None of your business, lady.
It is because a lot of them have that ball in her other mouth. I noticed that's why
No
None of your business, lady.
Yeah, what the hell is that? What the hell is that?
Well, that's a I it says it's meta a I
Know that was real. I can tell that was real. That was actually real. I thought that was real. Oh my god
I don't know but either way, I'm not hiring to be an escort
I
Boy breezes here. What's a bad boy breeze?
They were like I next was like paper on her feet like she don't have a shoe she wears like
What do you mean? I get expensive
Look at Kim, man.
Psyche, what is it? Bad Boy Breeze? Can he join?
Yeah, of course. Do you want to come up Bad Boy Breeze?
If you feel, yeah, I know you tried last time.
Bad Boy Breeze.
That's a cool one.
Tell him and try it on his phone. It's easier that way because now it's like the browser or whatever.
You got to mess with it. It's not like it used to be before.
Yeah, I like that.
Your green, your background looks like the Wizard of Oz.
Bad Boy.
Thumbnail?
I don't know.
Are you going to do on it?
Get to the bed.
My best friend Kudo's.
Kudo's too.
My best friend Kudo.
Aw, it's Saturday.
Yeah.
It's Saturday.
Yeah, well, you know, Toto was the smartest in the movie because Toto figured out he was memory jump out of the basket
Yeah, and he escaped the you know
and
By the Glinda to kill my Glinda rich because it was like her enemy like a mom
Can I say one thing earlier psyche you can ask him? I did play this song one of my favorite songs
Not even just from the Wizard of Oz. It's like
Trim, trim, yaw, trim, trim, yaw.
Mario Land of Gals.
That's how I left the day away.
The Mario Land of Gals.
I'm gonna make it so you don't have to authenticate me.
the
And then it'll tell you he can shut off his camera when he's backstage. They're not gonna see him
Joe you're why are you flirting with good times? I saw you pull. I saw you like you're flexing for oh
That's one of my favorite pastimes. That's one of my favorite pastimes flirting with good times like
On to your floor with me and I ever said like good
I'm sure not going to go to jail in two weeks when you're at a court
Oh my god, and it can't be all because it's going to jail
Okay
Well, I mean it's I would I just want to show you the thumbnail for that video that was put out saying because it's like
You know, this is supposed to be Brandon and I and X. I mean, it's like it looks a little bit strange
I mean, yeah, don't be Sean. It's just ridiculous. I want to show it
It's crazy take a look it's take a look it's crazy look at this picture
of the
And then dating we're not dating. She's the one that put us together and she said I like the way when you guys talk
You know cuz she wanted him to get support and stuff and we started talking we don't talk every day
Yeah, not at all
Talk come and help support him again
Yeah, a while back
Support these nuts support these
My tongue Joe get over here
Cuz I can be
again I've been the link and maybe it will work this time I mean I just um I'm sorry it's uh yeah
let's see pin the legacy of clumsy joints like I mean the let's see me
oh
Yeah, so Joe, what's going on?
Remember in the Wizard of Oz, when they're terribly lying,
like they're walking down that hallway,
and he gets scared of the wizard, he runs back,
and he jumps, and he dives off the platform through the glass.
He jumps to the window, and there's a shape of the terribly lying in the window,
and he jumps out of the window.
Yes, hell yeah. I'm so glad you remember that.
This is like, I'm not gay, but you are one of my best friends, bro.
I mean there's I don't care who the fuck cares about it. You remember the same right now
Yeah, anybody up here wants to fuck with son B. They're gonna fuck with me. You understand you fuck
Oh
There was one little person
Sorry, she's yelling at you
from The Wizard of Oz
and she played in a couple of movies
and she played in a TV series
but she played the corner
on The Wizard of Oz
Who is she?
Alright, that's a little
Who was it?
Was it that lady from Little People Big World?
Do you remember the principle from candy garden cop and the girl
I say something real quick. Do you remember that like blot like members you just said a minute ago like that
Was it that blonde lady from like?
Remember that blonde little midget lady that thought she was big shit
I would've fucked her. I swear to God, I would've fucked her.
I would've fucked her.
I would've fucked her and threw her out the window.
Like a cigarette, I would've fucked her and just threw her out the window.
Yo, where you got me on a door if she's normal size?
Here's some cute.
Yeah, come on, guys.
It's a little.
I can actually get that right.
Here's the video. Here, say goodbye. Say goodbye.
I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. I
I
Stop let me take a picture
Jerk all to it later. I'm not a pervert. I just want to jerk off to your fucking suitcase
My god, we have a guest. Oh my god
Oh, wait, you like that, um, you like that, Joe, hold on a second, where's my kid?
All the way from Calvary to Los Angeles, California.
Wow
So I'll be worried if she don't get home like I want to know she got home
You're like listen walking home nowadays like somebody just like kidnapped me and kill you
So I'm just
It is getting crazy. Oh, it's sitting. What up, man? Oh, it's big brother. It's not saying it's big brother
Everything's all the all Mexicans are the same person. They think everyone thought Alvaro was
Because the key has cats. They're like, oh
Picture
I was bad boy still in the chat
Bad bad. Where's bad boy? Where's that bad boy?
I got a new kitten, from outside, I just took in, got her in.
I'm naming her kitty like my a cat that passed away at age 20. So she looks like her
Can I be your bad boy? No
I do real life. Yeah, I like his avatar the glowing 300
Yeah
It's kind of like talking to my great-grandmother like at least there's a 90 year old lady
What what do you mean you said I had a great voice I don't sound old like that man. I sound better than you
No, I'm not she said
I'm not even I don't know where you're making me 15 years. Yeah older. Yeah, don't you know, don't stop
I don't know you like that. Yeah, you don't know
See looks older than me
Whoa, I've never seen you before. Huh? I
Nobody
Know a few people know me the ones that I know and trust friends. I don't just go
Yeah
I
Don't never show her. So she's got
I'm not gonna do it on YouTube. This is a trolling thing. No, I don't
YouTube like that
I got on YouTube to make videos and I was involved with rescue because there's another channel that I share with somebody else that
We've had a few years
Alarm not in there to rescue you have Kim rescue me
What are you eating, Glowstar? What are you eating? What is that? Fruit? Oh. Oh, wow.
Is it in my noodle? Supreme pizza? Oh, Supreme pizza. Yeah, I got some
noodle yesterday, and then we celebrated my birthday. So, yeah, you know that, I got some
Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah
Let me say this I went to my family's house in New Orleans and they had crawfish and when you crack that crawfish over to you eat the brain
Please let me finish let me be a sweetheart. I felt like so much smarter when I eat the brain of that little bug
I was like dad now. I'm smart
Look at me
And my dad was like, why are you yelling at me?
And I was like, because I just hate that bug.
He's like, just calm down, calm down.
And I'm like, you know what?
He's like, Joe, just don't do it.
And I was like, fuck you all.
I'm a bug.
All right, go ahead.
I'm just fucking with you.
Thank you like this.
You know what you should do.
I put it up, but you don't let me know what you should do.
I only eat the tails. I can't do the head there. You know, just eat the heads. That's looks gross
Did you ever even surrender they have that brown line of shit down their back?
I see that I would take that off. I pull it off because that's what what is in vain or something
Wow, I even sign each other
I'm sorry. Okay. I don't know. I think I thought you were talking.
It kind of reminded me of Suggie because he has like a turd running down his back as well.
Excuse me, Edward. I was going to stop it.
If you mind, I must throw one cigarette and I'll call it a day.
Just let me let me light it up.
Yeah. If you light it, if you light it in my butt.
I must do this white guy in real life. I'm a slap.
Joe?
Or me.
Bah!
Joe why watch your hands watch it when I see them in real it's not me in the ass. Okay, perfect
Yep, well, I talked to this guy on jokers last night
He was his name was pay pay or Peyton and he was like really interesting
If any piece of shit ever tried to put their hands on I next I would have the protector because I'm not gonna sit here
And let my friend get their hands
You can talk all you want
But I next is a friend to me, so I got to defend my friends
She's a good friend. I mean it's like
Now she's a great friend
Are you virgin? I thought you had sex with your wife
Yes, I am actually no I am virgin
You want to break it you what you're hymen
you guys blow
Oh, yeah, you guys blow fireworks. Oh my god
Half of there is like so many Mexicans in the streets yesterday because it was a firework show and my city was great
Yeah, they were always saying Spanish words like
Cheeto like bigger and he was like 19 that beat it was like mind people underage
Wow
And then you wash your big I'm just saying a person that buys like underage people liquor. That's really weird
No, you're all sami eclipse everybody imagine if it wasn't beaten somebody else bought a kid like sami
No, I'm talking to my cat. I'm talking to my cat. I'm sorry.
Oh, what's your cat's name, sweetheart? What's your cat's name?
Kitty. I named her Kitty. My name is Tom.
Wow. What are his real names? Oh, baby.
Shout out Kitty. For real. Shout out Kitty.
Shout out Kitty. You know, the person, the name of the first cat in Egypt was
I mean it wasn't a sweetie. It was like the cat is not prettier than my cat. Is there
any wild German lady or yeah. Appears and you don't gotta call her wild. He describes
yourself as wild Joe. Oh, okay. My bad. My bad. What a wild bitch.
Okay, Neil. I'm sorry if I was inappropriate because you're like, I don't know. I don't know. I'm sorry. I just don't know who piece of people are
I want to know what kind of cat glow star has he said he's got a beautiful cat
Is a white pussy
Yeah, the breed
Uh-huh gonna show it
No, I'm talking about your cat your your pet
No, he was gonna show his privates to Joe no
I'm gay. Oh, is that the door to you? Oh, that's he's a cat
Her name is
Can you show
Right now, but I can show what her name. I don't care. What is her name?
racial slur
oh my god
that's a lot sorry for asking
sorry for asking
there's a chatter named racial slur
I think she's insane
why is there white
because I'm white I'm 100% European
you can't help with that
no the cat
I was 100% gay
no you're 100%
cats are girls so they're lesbians
Well, I'm a this is an LGBT friendly show. So
Joe here
Then I got this cat
You like the cats I next yeah, that's a bit. Oh, so you got to how many cats you got three cats really. Oh, that's cute
Oh, look at the kiddie. Yeah, I got
Yeah, me good. I got on you have how many none because I'm out loser none
No, these are rescue cats is there because there's already a big enough
Man, I'm gonna I'm gonna rescue, you know rescue 911 where I got my cap from from a box a box
It was male to you
I'm a freeway.
Freeway.
Oh, I think I was held.
I think a similar to how Lola was held.
Oh, man.
Joe eats Buttons.
What?
Who the hell said that?
Who the hell just said that?
Is that true, Joe?
Well, technically they're right, actually.
Technically they are right.
Okay.
I wish I had a piece of Butters.
A Butters?
Right.
Yeah, I thought he was sorry. It was gonna get naked too. That's why I only joined. Oh
But
Yeah, they get bitch. Are you talking to me? Hey, you said good night, bitch
Black or G I'll take care of you real quick. Oh, sure. So you run your mouth. Oh, you want black or D got you where you wish
Oh, bitch as Nick
Who are you talking to Joe?
Uh, I'm not talking.
Okay, I heard something.
Did I sound like I was talking when I said words?
Here's something. No, I'm talking to my baby cat. She's right here in my face. Kim was back in the house
I was gonna say call the police
Hey, who's here bash be a forest play superfan Joe
Says I said forest fire, but it says Joe shipply
Is that your account Joe?
Oh my God, it actually is me.
I'm actually drunk enough to go on to the on-board.
I run Joe.
You know, Joe made out with me in my house.
And it was, it was, that, yeah.
I swear to God, the last thing I'd do
when it's Earth is make out with you, make good.
Yeah.
He would like, he would love to shoot his tongue up my butt
for the gun, right?
And your tongue's a bullet, right, Joe?
And Minecraft?
Joe?
Hello. Just the fact that you're saying that makes me want to bite you right now.
Oh, I love it. You're saying I'm just so much like I love your butt.
Yeah. But I'm more so much like I love anybody's butt if he had an ex's butt.
That's the butt of each other. No. I think I should know you well enough for that.
No, I don't do this online thing or whatever, you know. Well, guess what? Nice to meet you.
How about be a little bit, lick your butt.
Oh baby be the come on baby be the truth
Bronzeberg will lick your butt for sure. He's such a blood buzzer
He's like
I'm not saying I love be the wrong saying I will lick away her pain
It's not lick away your pain. I will
I'll lick it away. I just want to go away. Okay. I want to get that out there. Oh, okay. Maybe who is it?
Is it bringing the bringing more? Oh, no, it's I heard a cat meowing and my baby was looking out the window. Oh my god
with all this stuff going on just make sure it's not one so
Yeah, thank you. There's this guy. Let me say one thing. There's this guy that owns this house, obviously
Like it's a shitty house. It's not like a rich house like a shitty house. Okay, but when it was so cold this winter
I thought all these cats were gonna die because
Can a cat stay alive in 10 degree weather or whatever?
And it was even lower to 10 degrees one day was zero degrees. Well, you have to like keep
And I'm warm room and but now they're not where wall did I see the cats and I'm like man
You guys got more balls than other you cats and I petted them and I
Cat oh my god
Hello, do you have pets Joe? I had a dog but it does. Oh
Sorry
Yeah, and then and then I just don't want to get no more pets cuz like I don't want to I don't need the paint
Painful part, you know
Gorilla
But I'm here you go. You got trees. That's what if I get a pen. I will get a gorilla
I would why actually speed up a gorilla already know beat us. That's
Time on the phone that he said he's getting a pet otter
I do remember that actually.
I actually do remember that.
Or maybe Steel or something.
I was like, what the hell?
He's like, I don't have a lake, and I don't think you ever got it.
But that's what I'm saying.
Yeah, he was like, I'm a Navy SEAL.
Like, well, put the Navy aside.
You're just a SEAL.
Look at that.
You're a fucking retard.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Whatever the fuck a SEAL does.
Who said that he's I can't take another scandal. I mean last month go set a scandal
You're talking to some retarded that is true. Let me say that we'll say one thing no more scandals guys
One scandal is enough
Real no more scandals guys, please
He came on the stage like oh my god, you know, let's just say when you're not no one was listening
And they're like, hey, did he really say that?
He's fucking his dog, he's fucking his dog.
And I was like, well, Ghost, you just
say that you misheard you.
And he said, oh, I just misspoke.
I mean.
And that's how you want things to be without misspeaking.
I would fold eye next up like a pretzel.
I would show her a good sign of medicine.
She would be like, damn, boy.
No, I won't.
I
know
Alexander has Tommy James. Now you have your gender. Um, Joe
No
I don't do ginger
Ginger's Joe
I like ginger
No ginger
I like Spanish guys
Not Mexican, but nice ones. Yeah, I like half American guys
I don't like hillbillies either, you know, it's I'm nuts. You're our car
Really cuz you're a hillbilly
Did you ever see the buddy? How about the Beverly hillbillies? They were funny
Oh, that's so yeah, that was funny. That was I was a little kid when I saw that
No, because I don't have that I saw Joe Bishley is a drunk hunt
Because I don't do this
Weird people I don't know online. Uh-uh. No, I'm not like that. I'm not a host
Yeah, I just don't like that. I'm sorry
Oh, I'm weird. Is that what you're saying? It's like
Thanks, you say
Yeah, psyche the this baby likes the temptations the temptations treats. I got her
We love those temptations.
Oh, and they're gonna be happy that I got her because they wanted me to have her but they warned me
They said none other people try to take her and she kept running back and that she scratches
So I went over there with the towel and I didn't even need it because she recognized me from eating her people
So she's here enjoying the temptation treats and she's eaten a lot
She just needs to put on some weight because she's thin
So we got you have a mustache like they have whiskers that she
Who who
Come on Joe, no, I'm not beat. I don't have hair all over my face
No, nothing like that. I'm normal plus she's never been to Iran from from what her friends said
So, you know, she was born in Michigan and she's been here in the States since I
She's not American so she my mom is Bolivia
Yeah, well, a lot of background, Psyche. Psyche, a lot of background. My mom had, my mom's mom was German. She was, she was in a Holocaust before she was born and they got her out of there and they came to South America.
So I'd I'd rather prefer I wish I was born in Bolivia like my sister was
I'm actually wearing a dress right now. Like I'm Scott
It's a kill
Yes, how the Scottish
Bagpipes and stuff my dad liked that stuff
I mean, it's like beautiful, you know.
Was that a bag light?
Was that what your professional bag looks like?
Come on, come, there you go.
Come on, share.
You gotta share.
Don't be bullying her.
That sound.
Come on, come on, you can share with her.
Don't take it away from her.
And the bully cat's over here.
Yeah, she's.
Don't take it away.
Yeah, trying to take her treats.
You ate enough. Come here. Don't don't do that. My treat
She's trying to bully the baby
Here I'll give you some
Sam in a good life like that be a tree like a same my boy Sam in my life that be a tree
I mean like your balls like my show we say Air Force Sam around here
Cuz they don't have that other channel so he's not saying
He's always also I think he's like this guy. He's some last his kid cuz he's always like leave Alex Lou
Yeah, who is that weird person? It's some weirdo
Oh, yeah. See, that's what I hate the way she flip flops with everybody against them and then, you know, just her shows just went to trash. That's what it is. And she thinks people hate watch her. It's just it's stupid.
I mean, they do.
I mean, it's like, you know, but there's still you. I mean, it's like, that's fine. Who is that by the way.
Well, we ignore it, and those good friends that I've known for a long time, they ignore
it, and they don't participate in any of that, and they were going to join Alex, now they
see what she is, and so they don't want anything to do with her, and warn me.
They said, just ignore her, she's trashed, and they don't want to be involved with it.
Those are Bita's ex-friends.
Well, he has a whole trail of, you know, these bodies behind her, I mean, I mean, so, yeah, everybody left her.
Yeah, her ex couldn't deal with the internet, so he left her.
Yeah.
He doesn't know who where's your axis who the fuck ever loved
He's here. I'll talk to him. I've got one of his cats, you know, he wasn't good with the cat
He took in and busted the leg. So I wasn't gonna be with him anymore. So he was uh, he lived
Near me and he was evicted. He was he was a drunk. I don't like drunk people
Well, we're saying Pete is not here like why are you got attack?
No, because he was trying to attack and good cuz she goes back and forth with people lies
And I have her text where she gave me all this information on Alex
It was in I have it in when she wanted Alex in jail and she said you got to go here and report her
I have that it wasn't a threat towards her. It's just I'm tired of this two-faced back-and-forth and shit and hate bonding and
You know, I know better people than that that don't do it and we're cool and they tell me to just stay away from Vita and
Alex and they don't want anything to do with them and so I'm doing that
So we were on the phone earlier
They're good friends that I've had and they sent me some nice beautiful gifts and flowers
for my birthday
Yeah
No, I'll shove it up here. Well, no, it's too pretty to shove up your ass, but I'll shove some bushes up your ass if you want I got
Yeah, but it was nice that they always send gifts and we send stuff to each other and then also we can send like
Olive Garden stuff because I'm gonna give that friend a
Meal for her family at Olive Garden and you do that you can do it through that app that I sent the Starbucks through
Because I did that last year, because she always sends me beautiful gifts for Christmas
and birthdays, and I appreciate that that they did, and now these flowers are coming
through.
so they're great next
I'll say what they move is that now because you get rude and and you're drinking and
To be around people that are drunk and belligerent to you. So yeah
All right, well, I'm gonna say something bitch. I was talking about you're a bitch. You're not gonna call me a bitch
That's that's your woman there that you call a bitch and you know, I don't like you joe. I thought
That's why I don't deal with people they're drunk. I get so many begging bitch
I will put bacon bits in my salad all day.
So I'm gonna give a fuck less than a fucker's seat.
And I don't give a fuck about you.
So you need to shut up and stop being rude.
No wonder that woman went home.
Don't be rude, sweetie.
Well, okay, well, I want to say, let me see.
You got a share.
You got a share, Kitty, come on.
Okay, here you go.
Wow
We're gonna say Joe, but say something polite
But I think she's oh my god
I'm picky I'm picking I know you the pick I am
Oh my god. Yeah, just like that. I'm just kidding. I would not. No, I would not. Well, no, that's
a cute move.
People can move kind of fast. Like I said, in the second date, lesbians will bring out
a U-Haul to their second day.
U-Haul.
Somebody did say that guy, BG, like you or whatever. When you fuck that guy, BG.
Who fucks BG? Not me.
You would
Hey, play Joker
I need Joker to fly out to me. I mean, it's like I would love to see Joker. He's madly in love with me
I know I love my
Extend and I can't can't see to the get but we'll see each other someday and we'll be happy finally and I mean it's like this yeah, you know
I don't care, you know, he's 26 years old and I'm, you know, I'm 20 years old, but I don't care
what people say about me. His mustache is so cute. And he's an adult. I mean, I can get drunk
with him and smoke weed. Yeah, he's 26. That's a 26-year-old adult. Yeah, but now I'm not being
called like a, you know, the worst thing in the world now because they're saying he's like,
No
Embryo
Yeah, Brandon Q said he like Danny embryos
And I think why he's like, well, I didn't know they were sorry when I said you were dead. I'm so sorry
Who I remember?
He's uh, I'm sorry when I said you were an old piece of shit. Okay. Well, I'm not
He's drinking
Oh my God, you want to get that from Psyche, Joe?
He does.
I was thinking about it, but I thought you were talking to Joe before.
I was telling Joe guys, this guy used to bring flowers to his wife every day.
He used to bring like one a day or something like that.
And then when they brought her a huge bouquet, and then she's like, where do you want me to put those?
Where do you think I'm gonna put these he's like, well, you should probably put them in a vase. He's falling asleep, huh?
You happy, huh?
Yes, when I go to bed like look at what I'm saying see this fucking like that right here
Right there is a bed. I close all my vets in my house. It's sent to my bedroom
So all the air blows into my bedroom, so it's like a nice box up there
I love to sleep in the summer time where I wake up. It's like I'm in a nice box and I'm cold
Just goes up in the wall remember that Betty had them so cool it just goes up in the wall in the basement
I want to jump all the bridge and die. Oh my god, Joe. Well, you ask Christina about it. She knows all about it. She organized the bridge jump for you without a parachute. I want a parachute and I have to say a song.
No, that's not going to happen. She said no.
Who would have bet?
My pecanese will attack.
You know
Yeah, they were saying like you're a hillbilly or something anyway. So, you know, I hillbilly I'm not from here
I was you know, this is
Where you're right? Yeah
I don't even like this
Listen, the leading English was my third language
You know, I mean that consider myself more South American than
My first language like I
So whoever said that is a hillbilly and they've never been outside of this country and then they're looking an old picture
Yeah, that's ridiculous
I'll put beta's picture. I think that's beta. Oh my god. Yeah, let me go ahead and put her picture
Yeah
Why does it jealous of her?
Because you're jealous of me.
No, because that's her, that's her alt.
I can remove that psyche, that's ridiculous.
That's really, really good.
That means so jealous of me.
Yeah, that's what you highlighted.
You know, I'll report that profile.
I'm sorry, I didn't see, I didn't see, I didn't see, I didn't see.
Yeah, you, yeah, you're a bunch of banners.
I mean, that's ridiculous, you know.
I'll come up with these pictures.
Yeah, I want to report that account. That's ridiculous. That's Vita
You're a bitch man, shut up, but you know, Joe, I don't like talking to you. You're weird and you're drunk all the time
I'm weird, but you're gonna report me. Yeah, you are you're drunk man. You're you're weird and you're always drunk
You need a sober up and no wonder kim left
Yeah, but the thing is, I drink it, that's why I'm drunk, but you're not, you don't even drink it, and you, and you, and you, and yeah, I'm not a drunk, I'm not a drunk.
I don't like men like that, you know, so I don't I don't like that shit
You got to respect
Well, no, she's the one that started it and everybody knows that that's why she lost her friends and that's why she has nobody but the internet
Yes, she did her friends. I talked to them even her ex a friend curly
You know, they've been done with her her kia left her because she's too involved with the internet
And we were all talking about that her the people that she knew
It's just sad that she changed a lot and Kea left her because she's so involved in the internet
She doesn't have real life friends or anything
So if I have if I have to expose all that I will okay, so don't talk to me
We're gonna be a jerk and defending this stupid bitch. It doesn't show herself. That's not her. We've seen her everybody
Yeah, well, then you are then you're the one that bringing it up so don't talk
And you need to show Kim respect you dumbass you're an asshole to her
Yeah
No, well, she doesn't show me respect. So why should I she doesn't show anybody respect
Everything
Okay, all right, well, I don't want to talk to you I'm here to talk to psyche
Joe you blew it. Hey, I have nobody else with you. You don't know people
Nobody talks you weird. Oh, they play laugh. You're you're drunk and poor Kim. You're verbally abusive towards her
I hate shitty guys like that. You call me a weird, you know people like that belong in jail. Fuck
Yeah, you're the one starting you're drunk all the time
No, not already guys I've done some really good guys that are good cool, you know
They're evil. I knew this was a redhead. Let me see. I'm surely McLean? I'm not sure I'm
McLean. Hold on. Surely long. Surely long. They all seem evil. Who is his n-word? Oh my
god. There's a, who is that? It's a sentence, the machete. Okay. Oh, that's AstroMum. You
know what? I have AstroMum's real picture. Yeah, that was AstroMum. Yeah, I have it.
I'll put her picture on my profile because that's what she does. Oh, I don't think that's a little
Yeah, that's her. She does that. Yeah, she does that she won't yeah
Jetsons and I think that they have a dog astro and I think of like, you know,
Jetson
Yeah, well, do you know that um our phones today have more?
Computer power then the phones that send people to the moon and yet we can't go back to them. Oh, really?
No, I didn't know with the phones that
Say what a dumb ass thing to say
I just said, why is it not?
Oh, we went to the moon where my phone don't know what to do.
Like, nigga, shut the fuck up.
It's like I swear to God if I met you, I'd knock you up.
Because you hear it, there's a lot of people
who go to the moon with my phone in the moon,
and there's less of a delay than there is, you know,
you're calling Arizona.
Do you want to see a moon right now?
Do you want to see a formula?
Because I want to share my answer.
I want to share my answer.
I'm just asking. Do you want to see a moon or not, bro? No, he wants to moon you you
I don't want to see it. Actually, I don't know
Thank you
Stike you follow the what's going on with the the space scientists and all that
Where's my balls that they they have this documentary on Netflix. I don't remember that story
It was in 2016 and it's true and they don't know what happened to this kid
He was German and he went to Malta for a vacation
He was 17 and he went on his own with his girlfriend
and then she went back home and so he went to a cliff on a bike or he was he he rented a bike
and he disappeared six days later they find his body below the cliff and they said there's no way
he fell off the cliff because his head or no broken bones but when they found him they found
that he didn't have a brain and it's like how would they take it out because there was only two
the
It's already I mean, what do you what do you think it's aliens or I don't know but it's it's they have a documentary now remember that because they were
They
He wouldn't cut up or anything
They just found them like that it's like how do the organs disappear and it just three holes drilled on this side of his head right?
I mean, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there, I'll be there,
Hi, yeah, hey, you know, and my song my theme song was called dance to the mystery. Joe. Do you remember the theme song?
The tarot move
Okay, I'm gonna play something, but I was gonna play it. I'm gonna pull not gonna play that one
But I'm gonna play I was looking for something
With that would have to do with the scientists so home
Yeah, I mean that you can share that video. I shared it to my community post. Yeah, I mean I can't play the Netflix
Oh, okay. Yeah, no, it's not Netflix. It's a YouTube, but they have a Netflix show documentary
Okay
Yeah, I have a short video. This is called play would you rather would you rather
Do the Taylor Swift wedding or do you like to do the the black mirror metaverse?
Whichever one you want to play. Hey, I'll do the black
Okay, so this should be interesting. So we can just take this out comment on it as we go along and you'll like this
Okay, it'll be cool. Let's see
Okay
Here we go
I'll come in as I go along, but I'll say it right now and nobody's gonna come up here and solve my mom. Maybe that's what I know
Nobody's talking about it. You're the only one saying it's saying her name
It is time for us to adopt a new company
to encompass everything that we do
To reflect who we are and what we hope to build. I am proud to announce that starting today
Our company is now
This will do it
Now all we got to do is pop this into the drive and you're good to go
Thank you so much
But I have a question for you sure
Wouldn't you rather just leave?
What you said the outside you is in a coma, right? Which house are our doppelgangers?
Look a lights and then there are double takes blink your eyes and say is that who I think it is
KMVC 9s Christa Tatchel shows us how one very famous chiefs player might be mistaken for a time traveler, Krista
You are live at the Alexander Majors House Museum.
Don't know who Alexander Majors is.
Well, they were just like in Kansas City, everyone knows.
There you go.
Is that a woman?
A visitor to our museum had taken a picture
of Alexander Majors.
Oh my God, Alexander Majors.
They think that it might be Travis Kelsey at the time.
That is so funny.
What the what?
Ooh.
Alexander Majors is probably most famous for being one of the co-founders of the Pony Express.
Oh my God, this is great. This is great.
Now I wish I'd paid him off.
Sue battered the Pony Express.
I don't know what anyone named Clara.
I don't know.
I thought maybe she was a girlfriend of yours, party high involvement in such a social relationship here in 1885
Marley is back in 1888 right there 88 as a scientist
I can never take that risk. We gotta know where it is
Do you remember last week's town meeting when you volunteered to meet the new school teacher at the space you went to came in?
Oh yes, I told you.
Well, we just got word she's coming in tomorrow.
Here are the details for you.
Thanks for all your help.
At any time, you're misplaced.
back into your old head so I could go oh that wow he doesn't look at you out there is kind of
brain dead i'm sorry about that but if we copy across your consciousnesses would merge and your
experiences would fuse and you'd be back in my body back in my life mm-hmm he was on a football player
Solid. Really solid. Solid.
He was probably during his heyday about as famous as Travis Kelsey is today.
We met Travis Kelsey.
There's a strong resemblance there, huh?
I don't even know. This is a black and white picture.
Are you a man traveler?
I have some Marty McFly's, but that's about as close as I get to time traveling.
All right, hey, don't take that.
That's the way it was, me and Jennifer.
See, we could give our eyes off each other.
God, Jennifer, damn, I hope she's all right, but I can't believe we just left her there on the port!
Don't worry, Marry, she'll be fine!
When you burn her over that in 1955, the normal timeline was restored!
That means once we're back to 1985, you just have to hold her house and wait for her up!
Yes!
Go south!
And look into both?
I'm newly tethered to the ship.
If you exit into your old body, that ship gets wiped.
crew would be wiped too, so it really is one or the other.
We're hoping that Travis will consider blessing us with a visit.
We would love for him to come out and learn a little bit more about the frontier of Travis Kelsey.
Oh, he really saw it!
There is a revolution coming.
Excuse me? What do you mean?
The future is staring back at us like a perfect return glass.
In this future, it must be protected.
What's it got to do with me?
Look, what is that?
You've changed everything.
You look a bit nervous, hey?
Thierry, what's it like to stand in the FIFA World Cup Stadium?
Wouldn't you like to know?
Why is he just telling you?
Just tell me.
I'm over.
Come on.
It's not something that you can put into words.
Such a tease.
You can't rush it.
You will find out when it's your time.
Thanks to the wisdom coach
So
Now I'm going back to Suriname
Here's the walk that you've been waiting for
Actually, the world cup's been waiting for me
Man, that's why they want to stop it. They will come after you without cease
because the future
belongs to us
That's the spirit. Just remember who drove you here.
Inspiring every step of the next legend.
The official natural carrier proudly sponsored by Kia.
Inspiration connects us all.
Alexander Major's birthday was October 4th.
Travis Kelcey's is October 5th.
You know, they're practically twins, just about 175 years between them.
Well, I guess Ms. Clayton will have to find another transportation.
I never meet a woman with no possibility of a romantic infatuation, right?
You're the doc, Doc.
All right.
Get to the lawyer and get ourselves back in the future.
Oh, listen, Doc, it's horrible in the gas tank when I was landing,
so we're going to have to patch it up and get some gas.
You mean we're out of gas?
Yeah, it's no big deal. We got Mr. Fusian, right?
Mr. Fusian powers the time circuits and the flux capacitor.
But the internal combustion engine runs on ordinary gasoline, it always has.
It's not going to be a gas station out here until some time of next century.
Gasoline. You can't get the DeLorean up to 88 miles per hour.
88.
So what do we do?
LG. Oh man. A perfect picture on Mars.
I've already told you, the future is staring back at you.
The museum directors here have reached out to Kelsey's foundation saying he can
be a guest here anytime they would love to have him come by Christotato KBC 9
News. All right, thank you. Well tomorrow for
Wednesday only the museum will have a new name the Travis Kelsey House Museum
and a mission is $8 a person. And then it was such a hit. It was way bigger than I
I think you have to. I think you like have to. They kill you if you try to walk away and they clone you
Which one do you want?
The matrix is everywhere. It is all around us
Even now in this very room
You can see it
Feel it when you go to work
When you go to church is back to the future the thing people ask you about most. Yeah, it's just you lately
Yeah, especially lately, but yeah, but I get all this questions about hoverboard 66 right now. That's here
now and and uh, I would say the one thing that they
You know, this is what you were supposed to look like they predicted you look like at 47 years old
a young Donald Trump in the middle of this.
Not a bad one.
And two family ties there around the neck.
That never really caught on, either.
It does look like Donald Trump.
Yeah, it does. There is a Donald Trump-y-ness to it.
Huge!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Yeah!
Are you dumb or what?
24!
No use, buddy!
Steve Aucasus calls to the world!
We'll run off 35, 25 hours an hour!
Yeah!
I am a senior that Donald Trump is the greatest president in the world.
Donald Trump has been pulled over your eyes to bring you from the truth.
Oh, how amazed were you to see your roaster up there with Starman just cruising along with the big planet
and how long will we be getting life used, do you think, from the car?
Well, I think it looks so ridiculous and impossible.
You can tell it's real because it looks so fake, honestly.
There is no way that technology is neutral, you know technology reflects the
elites, the passions, the capacities of the people that create and then continue to use it.
Once you start looking at the technology plus the culture
Those things together mean that the technology is constructed in a certain way, and it's understood in a certain way, and it's used in a certain way.
And once you start putting all those things together, then it has a purpose for the people that are talking about it, which is far from neutral.
Technology is always harnessed to a particular end.
Now, sometimes that can be positive or negative,
but it's not as simplistic as saying,
oh, it's up to people how they use it,
because people can only use it within the constraints
of how it's designed, the knowledge that they have,
and the society that they've been socialized in.
And those three things together
mean that technology has an actual cultural value,
Until we start asking those questions on what are the social costs and benefits and who is
excluded and what is the environmental cost of all this. I mean you know there are in terms of the
huge amount of
of toxic landfill from discarded mobiles for example. Yes and you know until we start looking at
those other pictures in terms of we look at the way that technology works as a sort of
as a network of production, but instead see it as part of a living world because technology
is not part of that living world. It has an impact upon that living world until we see those bigger
questions and technology in the broader scheme of things rather than just as its own story.
I think we're only scratching the surface of
the many ways in which we are using it to change ourselves and our futures.
Which movie is this?
We robots will ensure mankind's continued existence.
You are so like children.
We must save you from yourselves.
Don't you understand?
This is why you created us.
The perfect circle of production.
Are you letting him up? He was backstage.
My logic is undeniable.
Oh, he laughed? Yeah, because he was trying to get up.
I can see that.
The created must sometimes protect the creator.
Even against his God.
I think I finally understand why Dr. Lannan created me.
The suicidal reign of mankind has finally come to its end.
Oh my god
I was a human
Breathing and thinking
Eating and drinking
Fiddling
I was a human
Before you killed me
And ripped my heart
I knew what love was
Now when they ask me
I just reply slow
And sound like an iPhone
I do not know love
I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a robot, I am a
Please don't be rude on this.
No, I'm not. I'm watching.
Please don't be rude, I'm sorry.
Good night, guys. I miss you.
Oh, that's you, Inax.
No, that's Alex.
Because you had nobody in real life.
Oh, somebody's sleepy.
But really.
No.
How can you be sleepy if you don't know how to have a green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green green
No more dreams! No more dreams!
Looks like somebody's having a bad dream!
A bad dream!
Oh my god.
He went away.
Can you file these files please?
What the fuck?
Yeah.
What the fuck is that?
Hey, but wouldn't it be funny if one of these bars came alive?
Yeah.
I am a file, and you put documents in me, and a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do-do, a file, a do-do-do
But I was like, oh yeah, that's not even the same bucket, I am the cool guy, I guess,
laid back and sad, and now I'm tired of my life, but that's rude, no clothes, I like
What's your favourite idea?
Mine is being creative
How do you get the idea?
I just try to think creatively
When you look at this orange
Tell me please, what do you see?
It's just a boring old orange
And maybe to you, but not to me
I see a silly face
Walking along and smiling at me
I don't see what you mean
Cause you know, I don't like it, it's really not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all, not good at all,
That was I met
There's that movie tea
Yeah, that's we have messed up
Exist you got old like history stuff in the past but different to a mystery you made me die
What's it all about? You've no idea, and everywhere you look...
No!
I know!
I stream these, make your teeth go red!
Baaah!
The best plan is to live and go to space!
A rocket ship can go to the moon!
Stop!
Make it stop!
I keep your hand higher than you!
You've got documents in me!
Fuck your hand!
But where does one go?
You can't be crushed by a bus!
No, no, no, no!
I never go to!
What is that?
Thank you, Phil!
You should get your favourite thing!
Ah!
I didn't like it.
Oh my god, no, I'm listening go ahead. I'm listening. It's like what's the breaking bad news? Is it bad news or goodness?
So, okay, so we have
Gangs we have broomgangs photo guys. Are you ready to see broomgangs photo like broomgang? Oh, I thought you could see this nigga
This nigga runs his mouth so much. I can't wait to see this packet. Let me see this nigga. Ah
Oh my god, that's why I got gussed out by last week. Oh my god. What's up beat it as big as now?
What's up beat it as big as now fortunately Joe?
They also
Docs your photo to you, and I'm sorry to show you this. I hope you won't get offended. Look what they did to your phone
Oh, she
Show that if it's me. Don't you dare show that? Oh, well, actually that's actually pretty handsome. Thank you
But you don't see my photo they made of me
Yes, I do. Yes, I do
Oh, oh my god
Sorry, dude. Don't play that take that off. Take it off
Look like these people. I mean gosh, I mean everybody is here
Right in queue looks kind of boy look like an FBI agent. Well, I look like a fucking you know homeless person in my pictures
Leave me alone. Who looks like an FBI agent? Oh, that's right
What's the thing and Brandon was saying? Oh, I look like I look like I'm from the Matrix or I'm not a major in Smith
Or something and preference photos because he's just sitting there with the glasses and glasses and a sweatshirt
But I was like, okay, whatever, but you know what?
Oh, we have, we have a guest coming up. Okay. So, um, surprise guest. Um, race yourselves guys.
Yeah, I have a question. I have a question for psyche. If you guys don't mind
Yeah, if you guys don't hey psyche, I got a question for you, brother
Uh, what the fuck are you doing?
You know, you're a grown-up man. You have a grown-up panel. You're a great man. You're strong and beautiful. Why the fuck are you doing this?
You better stop you better you're playing yourself down as a bit you playing yourself as you playing yourself as a dumb dumb
Not even a victim. You're playing yourself as a dumb dumb
You better stop doing that
You're making these dumb ass fucking dumb ass panels by the way dumb ass AI shit that means nothing to no one
You're making yourself look even more dumb. What do you do? Pick me up? I'm going where the heck you back
You gonna kick me off the show?
The day's off of ruining the show, ruining the vibe, coming out and bitching, okay?
And just think about it.
Oh you want them to talk shit about you?
No, the pictures you mean the pictures that he's putting up. Yeah, that's kind of
Yeah, I run it with anyone nobody's gonna talk shit about my dude
Yeah, I guarantee that ain't nobody gonna talk shit. He can talk shit about himself. Hey, you you're not gonna do it
I know that that's in a real way
Any of you up here that won't talk shit. It's like you know, you can do it
My brother can do it to himself, but none of you would have say anything
I'm not talking to you Joe. I'm talking to her. I don't know if you're a female I transgender whatever you are Joe figure it out
Fuck you
And by the way, Joe you set up here you defend these you literally fucking
You make him on about it
No, you shouldn't do that you eggamondo
Well fucking you want it now Joe, I'll give it to you now
Yeah, I think you're a negative. I think you're a negative impression. I'm a boy you fucking make him do the
Worship ever and like you like to see that because it gives you more content and plus you laugh your sadistic about it
You laugh at this when you when psyche fucks up you laugh at it Joe you laugh
You shouldn't laugh at it, huh?
You ain't have my boy out at all. I'm up here trying to defend my boy. Don't get him drunk
Don't fucking tell him to do shit and don't fucking try to run his panel straight up Joe unless some drill shit
Let me talk to this bitch. It's your dog. I'm gonna beat you. Let me talk to this bitch though
Hey, you doing girl. What's your name? By the way, I don't want to disrespect you back on the bench. What's your name?
He is a big old
Your name's a piece of shit drunk
Yeah, he's drunk all the time. That's why I don't want you to get drunk all the time.
What should I, what should I, what should I, well, you, what should I, what should I say your name is?
Piece of shit drunk. I'll go with it if you really want.
I mean your fucking boys. I mean call yourself a fucking yeah
All right pieces drunk. You're the same thing as this fucking dining joe. You're a piece of shit, too
You are a piece of drunk. Good name by the way. You're trying to hit on my boy
You know, he's drunk. It's fucking trying to get a more drunk. You're trying to get him to do some dumb shit
Get off his dick. You're trying to live off his fucking. He's got more viewers to you and you're trying to live off his dick
Leave my boy alone
And that's in the real way leave him alone leave psych alone
He's the only reason he's doing that he's giving it to you because he thinks he's gonna get more fucking views
But you you're a no-name viewer at all. You're no name. No one's no one knows who the fuck either you are
The reason why suck it up here I have to try to explain my boy you just want some views we don't like you
You're fucking dumb dumb. We don't know who the fuck you is. We never knew who you were.
And we never will. And that's in a little way.
No, I'm not gonna leave me and sake you get weird on his panel. We'll talk about like Batman shit, but not you Joe
We don't want you here. You're you've ruined the panel
Fuck you up Joe keep playing with me
Saki's not here to be weird about the ship we can have a conversation
You know I'll get weird if you want to get weird with you girl, but you're not gonna do my boy like that. Yeah, I'm done with you
I'm talking to her. I'm talking to her
Ain't nobody gonna fuck with my boy up here y'all beating up psyche you ain't gonna beat up psyche when I'm around cut
You got me fucked up
Big Joe, I'm the big dog around here. How many fellas you got? How many fellas you got Joe? I'm the big dog around here. You ain't got a fuck up psyche.
Nah, you tried. You got, you tried, but you ain't gonna do it no more though.
And I'm putting a stop to it. I'm putting a stop to it right now, Joe.
You call me inwards, call me whatever you want. TLS. Do whatever you want. I'm putting it into it right now.
That's my boy. That's my boy. That's my boy
Nothing we're just gonna ban you at this point because yeah, we're just gonna ban you
Literally ban you when I didn't kick you out with a band shut the fuck up and be cool. Be a good boy and talk
You're not gonna be cool. I've been here. I'll be in your ass. Keep doing me. You got one more thing to do. I'll be in your ass, dog. Say one more thing, dog. I'll bend that ass, dog. All right, bag it. Bag it. Damn it, bag it.
than you would you say what was that last word you said can you repeat it real quick for the chat
It's what was bitch because that would you are no, that wasn't what you said though
What was that last one you said can you please repeat it for the chat
Can you please report that and can you please repeat the last word that you said sir
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Oh, you said sorry thank you, man
If you say sorry right now, let it go, but if you don't say sorry, I'm gonna burn that ass up there in a real way
I got more money than you
Guarantee I will literally make him take you right now. You better say sorry to me. You better say sorry to site here
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
obviously I want to play I want to I want to play I want to play for blood you
want to play for blood all right let's play for blood how you want to do who
asked more we can both call who asked more or who asked more money or who asked
more people how you want to play this because I guarantee he's gonna get along
with me
one phone call and you realize you're done right like that's one phone call
Would you like to be kicked out?
It doesn't matter, would you like to be kicked out?
Actually, man, I had that if I would kick you,
but I could be kicked, thank you, thank you.
You're the best.
Now, I want you to kick me though, I want you to kick me.
Cause you're like, you act like you can do everything.
Like, oh, you want me to tell him to kick you?
Like, yeah, go and tell him to kick me.
I want to see what he does.
Go ahead, sucky. You want to take his words?
I'm going to tell him to kick you.
How about that?
Where's Psyche go? I don't know probably kick that freak all this panel
This little cat is so thin though Joe, I hope she gained some weight
Yeah, I've only had her couple
Happy here like she's you know, she's been all alone
Rejected of her mom and she's still little
She must have been starving, but yeah, she's been eating and I had a teacher to use the litter box
She was all confused and lost and she's been outside. She's never been inside. So I got her before the fireworks
So I've never been a cat person, but um, oh and I do see those lonely sack cats
It does bring them her more heart strings, you know, I may that will get a cat actually maybe I will do a cat man
You know what? I've never had cats before either and I fell in love with them and out here they needed help
So I started taking some in because I was always the picnice or you know dog person and this one just really
Yeah, because you got a hard
A lot of people don't have that heart at least you have a heart world
And they told me good luck because nine people try to take her in and she comes running back
But she's been with me two days and she won't she follows me everywhere
And she's chill skinny and and I'm feeding her and she's just so happy and relieved and it's like
Yeah, just I love her
And she looks like the cat that my 20 year old cat that passed away in December.
Yeah, she's right here with me. She's so sweet.
One thing I will not stand is that freak.
Talking about my baby Vita. That is a friend to me and I'm gonna sit here
Or some other people don't get along and
And I play all day long
Yeah
They said I next is a piece of shit. I'm like a good boy
So you gotta watch out. Yeah, and me I have the backs of these rescues, you know, and I love them
Especially this little baby that just needs to gain weight. She's just so skinny, but they're gonna be happy tomorrow
So cute
Huh, what no she's over here trying to sleep here. I'm trying to make her get along with the bully keg
Coming looking at her. So she's right here with me. Just you know, you're so cute. You need to get some sleep. You're so skinny
decent eating
You're so sweet
Why don't I don't give a fuck? I don't give a fuck about being alone like maybe I'm alone, but I don't cry about it
I don't actually I'm happy about it
Yeah, I should be more mad at someone in my house. I didn't get the fuck out of here. So I'm trying to give you credit
Getting rude and just calling name
My baby you would kiss this yes, I do
You know this baby I think she's never had a home before she's she seems so happy and like in shock because she's been outside on her own since her mom
Rejected her
Yeah, she's so cute
Ready and you're beautiful. Oh, look see she's looking at my phone. She heard you. She's like what?
I know lay down. Come on. You can sleep
your bait
No more outside suffering. Okay. Come on
My next time gonna get off, but it was nice talking to you, but I will say this
Ever say
I'm going to break you, you understand?
I can break you, look, look.
I'm going to break you.
She's a wonderful show, okay?
You know, otherwise, she always wants to gang up on people,
and that's why she found YouTube.
It's sad.
The, okay.
I'll give you a trip back.
Yeah, what happened to Psyche?
He just disappeared.
What's the cast name that you saved?
Kitty.
I called, I named her Kitty.
She didn't have a name.
She was, she's a feral kitten.
I'm going to hop off and I want to thank you with let's go ghost come on and yell and then he's gone. Okay. You have a good night. Okay. All right. Bye. Thank you.
Thank you.
packed us a delicious chicken picnic.
Huh?
Exkey bee?
What's it all about you? No idea. And everywhere you look, all you see is hatred, and darkness, death, and fear.
But you know it doesn't have to be. But I hate you, and you hate me.
Cause even though we're different, it doesn't make a difference. And we can live in harmony.
No, you don't know who I am. But maybe I can hold your hand.
And together we can understand about love.
I feel tingly.
Yes, that's love, my friend.
And it's time for you to learn all about it.
feel like life's unfair. Everybody hates you and no one cares. But if you follow me, maybe
you will see. The love is everywhere. And what is love? Is it in the sky? No, it's a
feeling deep inside. Because I'm hungry. No, you're lonely. I can see it in your eyes.
I don't understand. Don't worry, we'll soon. Come and meet some of my friends. They know
all about love. Come on, just do it with a rainbow. Oh, there he goes. Fly through the
Maybe we should follow him, or we'll get left behind.
Yes, but there's lots of chicken left. I'd like to eat the chicken.
I'd also like to eat the chicken. Let's do that instead.
So here we are with all my friends, and they love you, all of them.
Yes, we do.
It is true. We love you.
You love us too.
I love you too, fairy boy.